I can't believe this.
真是不敢相信
MANGA ARTIST AIKA KAKUTA'S FORBIDDEN RELATIONSHIP WITH HER LOVER
（漫畫家角田愛華 與婚外情對象的禁忌之戀）
Right, you're a huge fan of her, aren't you?
對喔，你是她的大粉絲吧？
The way she draws heroines yearning for love
角田老師將女主角對愛情的嚮往
is amazing.
描繪的超棒的
But she's having an affair…
結果她卻外遇了…
Guess she wanted love from more men than just her husband.
她可能不只要丈夫 還想要更多男人的愛吧？
Guess that means she's having sex with others as well as her husband.
也就是不僅和丈夫 還和其他人發生關係了啊
-Were you a fan of her too? -Huh?
-香坂也是她的粉絲嗎？ -什麼？
You look troubled.
你的表情很陰沉
Ah, no.
啊，不是
Are you worried about what happened this morning?
該不會是在煩惱早上的事情吧？
This morning?
早上？
I saw Ms. Misono scold you for the mishap with the internal data.
我看到味園因為內部資料錯誤在罵你
That's embarrassing.
真是不好意思
Ms. Misono's gotten so strict since she became a manager.
味園升上主任後就變得很嚴厲呢
It was my mistake, though.
是我犯錯的關係嘛
Ms. Misono has her walls up so high.
味園感覺心防很重呢
I wonder if she's ever opened up to anyone else.
感覺從來沒跟別人袒露過內心的樣子
Oh! Do you know the rumor about her?
對了，你們知道她的傳聞嗎？
Rumor?
傳聞？
I overheard it in the girl's bathroom.
我是在女廁聽到的
Rumor has it she's a virgin.
聽說她還是處女
A virgin?
處女？
Later-in-life virgins are becoming common.
最近很多吧？高齡處女
I mean, not that it matters.
不過那也沒什麼吧？
It's their own choice after all.
畢竟是每個人的選擇
Come to think of it, a friend of mine
說到這個，我有個朋友
for some reason always dates girls who are virgins.
不知道為什麼，交往的女生都是處女
He said breaking down their guard is like doing construction work.
他說打破她們的心防就和施工一樣
Construction work?
施工？
UNDER CONSTRUCTION
（施工中）
In the 32 years since I was born
我從出生到現在的32年中
I have not had sex even once.
從來沒有過所謂的“性經驗”
Kosaka.
香坂
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
Oh, nothing's wrong.
啊，沒什麼
Sorry.
抱歉
The interview…
關於取材…
I've been doing a fairly good job getting by
成人出社會之後
as a working adult.
我的工作一帆風順
But when it comes to sex…
但唯有性經驗…
Ms. Misono, your earrings are really pretty.
味園，你的耳環很漂亮耶
My boyfriend gave them to me. Anyways, these documents…
我男友送我的，是說這些資料…
If she has a boyfriend, she must be having sex too.
她有男朋友，也就是說做過了吧？
You're not making clear what you want to say.
你沒有說清楚要表達的內容
-Redo from scratch? -From scratch.
-要重做嗎？ -重做
I wonder how it feels to be touched by someone else.
被他人撫摸身體，是什麼感覺呢？
It's not the same doing it yourself.
自己摸的話不太明白啊
I want to also be someone that has experienced sex.
我也想變成有性經驗的人
"We welcome women who want to have sex!"
“非常歡迎想愛愛的女性”
No way, never.
不行，不可能
That's definitely way beyond what I can handle.
再怎麼說難度也太高了
HEY HERE'S THE INVITATION TO THE REUNION PARTY CHECK IT OUT
（辛苦了，同學會的邀請 我寄給你了，看一下吧）
A reunion party…
同學會…
Your nails look different than usual, Kosaka.
香坂，你今天的指甲很特別呢
-Huh? -You usually keep them looking natural.
-是嗎？ -平常都是比較自然的樣子
Oh.
喔
I have a reunion today, so I went with something a bit fancier.
我今天有同學會，所以想打扮一下
The matte style you have is nice too, Ms. Kodaira.
小平的霧面風格也很不錯啊
You think so?
是喔？
It doesn't go down well with men, though. Especially because I'm ugly too.
但是這完全不是男生的菜 尤其我又是個醜女
By the way, I've been meaning to tell you, you don't have to be formal with me.
對了，之前就想和你說 不用對我這麼客氣啦
I'm just a temp, after all.
畢竟我只是派遣人員
Right.
好
Sometimes I have no clue how to answer Kodaira.
我有時候會不知道要怎麼回答小平
She has a fever?
她發燒了嗎？
I understand.
我知道了
I'll come pick her up right away.
我馬上去接她
-Was it from day care? -Yes.
-托兒所打來的嗎？ -對啊
It's the third time this month.
這個月已經第三次了
That's rough.
真是辛苦了
I have to prepare 50 copies of this document before seven…
我七點之前要準備五十份資料啊…
Shall I do them?
我來幫忙吧？
Thank you.
謝謝你
I'm really sorry.
真的很不好意思
It's fine.
沒關係
Okay, I'll make it in time.
好，趕得上
SORRY I'M LATE
（抱歉我遲到了）
I'M LEAVING THE OFFICE SOON SO I SHOULD BE THERE A LITTLE PAST EIGHT!
（我要離開公司了 大概八點後會到）
Huh?
咦？
Okay.
好
What?
怎麼會？
How do I fix this?
要怎麼辦？
PLEASE CONTACT EIKOU MAINTENANCE FOR USAGE GUIDELINES AND REPAIR REQUESTS
（如有操作或維修方面的問題 請聯絡榮光維修公司）
I'm from Eikou.
我是榮光的人員
Oh.
啊
Thank you for coming so quickly.
謝謝你這麼快趕過來
My name is Kosaka.
我叫香坂
Oh.
喔
Nice to meet you.
請多指教
EIKOU MAINTENANCE ENGINEER
（榮光維修工程師）
Kagiya, is it?
你是鍵谷，對吧？
I'm sorry to be rude, but I need the copies as fast as possible,
抱歉這麼趕，但我得盡快完成資料
so please hurry.
再麻煩你了
Yes.
好
I'll let you know when I'm done.
我修好了再跟你說
Oh.
喔
Okay.
好
Thank goodness, I'll make it in time.
太好了，趕上了
That'll be it from me.
那我先走了
Kagiya.
鍵谷
Thank you so much. You saved me.
你幫了大忙，真的很謝謝你
Alright! Cheers!
好啦，乾杯！
Your job is tough, huh?
你的工作很忙吧？
I just had a few issues come up.
剛剛出了點問題
Your nails are so cute, Maiko.
麻衣子的指甲好可愛
You think so? I'm trying a different color.
真的嗎？我試著用了不一樣顏色
How nice. I haven't had my nails done since I had my youngest.
真好，我生了小兒子後 都還沒做過指甲
I know, right? There's just no time.
我懂，連去指甲沙龍的時間都沒有了
My wife said the same.
我老婆也是這麼說
I see.
是喔
I would much rather have sex, like you can,
比起做可愛的指甲
than have pretty nails.
我更羨慕能做愛的你們啊
-Aren't you going to get married? -Huh?
-麻衣子不結婚嗎？ -什麼？
Do you have a boyfriend?
你有男朋友嗎？
Not at the moment.
暫時沒有
Actually, it's been ages.
其實是一直沒有
I'm sorry I'm late.
不好意思，我遲到了
-Oh! -Saeki, you're late!
-喔！ -佐伯，你太慢了啦！
Sorry. I had to work overtime.
抱歉，我今天得加班
Can I sit here?
我能坐這裡嗎？
Uh, sure.
啊，請坐
Long time no see, Kosaka.
香坂，好久不見了
I haven't seen you since graduation.
畢業之後就沒見過了呢
-Excuse me. -Yes?
-不好意思 -來了
-One glass, please. -Coming right up.
-我要一個杯子 -馬上來
S-Saeki, I…
佐…佐伯
Saeki was my first and last boyfriend.
佐伯是我唯一交過的男朋友
And the only one with whom I ever had that chance.
也是我唯一有過那種機會的人
I-I'm sorry.
抱歉
I never thought I'd go 14 years without another chance.
沒想到自那之後 14年以來再也沒有找到機會
-Who's up for an after-party? -Me!
-有人要續攤嗎？ -我！
You coming, Maiko?
麻衣子也要來吧？
I'm sorry. I have to get up early.
抱歉，我明天得早起
Really?
是喔？
-I'll pass on it too. -You too, Saeki?
-我也免了 -佐伯你也不去啊？
I live really far away. If I come along, I'll miss the last train.
我住得很遠 去續攤一定會錯過末班電車的
What?
什麼啊？
Have fun, guys.
大家玩得開心點
Okay, then. Let's go.
算了，那走吧
Everyone's exactly the same, huh?
大家看起來都沒變呢
Yeah.
對啊
They haven't changed despite becoming parents.
就算當了父母，大家也還是一樣
I wonder if he's married.
不知道佐伯結婚了沒？
I'm glad I made it today.
不過今天有來真是太好了
Huh?
為什麼？
I'm being transferred to Sendai next week.
我下週開始要調去仙台了
I'll probably be living there for a while.
大概會在那裡待上一段時間
I see.
是喔
The next time we meet may be 10 years from now.
下次和你見面，大概就是十年後了
In 10 years…
十年後…
Could this be my chance?
這難道是機會嗎？
If it's with Saeki, it could just be a one-time thing…
如果是和佐伯的話 可能就是僅此一次而已…
Huh?
嗯？
Are you okay?
怎麼了嗎？
Oh. Yeah.
喔，沒什麼
Later-in-life virgins are becoming common.
最近很多吧？高齡處女
He said breaking down their guard is like doing construction work.
他說打破她們的心防就和施工一樣
If I lose this chance I might never get it again.
如果錯過這次機會 恐怕一輩子就這樣了
Saeki.
佐伯
I have a really strange thing to ask of you.
我有一個超怪的請求
Can you try not to get weirded out by it?
希望你聽了不要笑我
I'm…
我…
A virgin.
是處女
Huh?
什麼？
It's weird, isn't it?
果然很怪吧？
Uh, no…
呃，不會…
Are you married?
你結婚了嗎？
Huh?
什麼？
Do you have a girlfriend?
你有女朋友還是喜歡的人嗎？
What?
呃？
If you don't mind…
你願意的話…
Could you do it with me?
能和我做嗎？
Pardon?
什麼？
No strings attached, just for tonight.
我沒有其他要求，就只有今晚而已
I won't tell anyone…
我不會和任何人說的…
So please.
拜託你了
Are you sure about this?
真的可以嗎？
Yes.
嗯
Of course.
當然
Do you want to take a shower first?
那你要先洗澡嗎？
Huh?
什麼？
I guess you're not sweaty. Never mind.
你應該沒有流汗吧，別在意
Ah…
喔…
Yeah.
嗯
So this is how it feels
被其他人撫摸身體
to be touched by someone.
是這種感覺啊
It's colder than I thought.
比我想像中的冷呢
I'll touch it, okay?
我要摸了喔
Okay…
好…
Does it hurt?
會痛嗎？
No, it's fine.
不會，沒關係
Can I put it in?
我要進去囉
Please.
拜託了
Ouch!
好痛！
Are you okay?
你還好嗎？
I-I'm sorry.
對…對不起
I got a little sweaty, so I'll go take a shower.
我流了點汗，我洗澡一下
Wait a little, okay?
稍等我一下
Why are you running away?
為什麼要跑啊？
This time I won't run.
這次我會努力不要逃跑的
Saeki!
佐伯！
What happened?
怎麼了？
Why are you leaving?
為什麼要回去？
Did I do something wrong?
我是哪裡做錯了嗎？
I can't do this after all.
我果然還是沒辦法
I can't do it with you.
我沒辦法跟你做
I'm sorry.
抱歉
Kagiya…
鍵谷…
Everyone else is able to do it,
大家都做得到的事情
so why am I the only one that can't?
為什麼只有我做不到呢？
Oh no!
喔，天啊
Come on…
真是的…
Dinner is ready.
晚餐好了喔
Miyuki.
美由紀
I'm busy, so don't talk to me.
我現在很忙，不要跟我講話
SHO, 27 YEARS OLD, TOKYO
（翔，27歲，東京）
You're Ren, right?
你是小蓮，對吧？
I'm Sho.
我是翔
Yeah. I'm Ren.
對，我是蓮
Shall we go to a hotel?
那要去旅館了嗎？
What?
什麼？
Oh. Okay.
喔，好
Is what I want really that much to ask for?
我想要的，真的是奢望嗎？
All I want is to have gentle sex.
我只是想要一段溫暖的性愛
It won't ever happen for me, will it?
果然和我一輩子無緣吧？
I never expected to talk about games here.
我沒想到會在這裡聊起遊戲
I have to go pick her up at day care.
我必須去托兒所接她
It's tough being a mom.
當媽媽真辛苦呢
Why does everyone only see me as a mother?
為什麼大家 都只看到身為人母的我呢？
I want to go somewhere private.
我想要去能兩人獨處的地方
Wait, does that mean…?
等等，這意思是？